mercycorps.org 2003-04-02

# Privacy Policy Mercy Corps

| 

Our goal at Mercy Corps is to extend trust and respect to you on the web. We are committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our website. The following information details Mercy Corps' collection, protection, and use of the data we receive from visitors to this website.

**Email Updates**

Emergency program updates provide a worldwide perspective on the Mercy Corps mission to alleviate suffering, poverty, and oppression around the globe. In order to receive these updates you must provide Mercy Corps with your email address. Rest assured, your email will be used for emergency and program purposes only, and we will NOT sell, rent or trade this information to a third party. Certain email update promotional activities may require your name for database recognition purposes. This information will be held in complete confidence, and it will NOT be sold, rented or traded. In addition, you will be given the option to remove your name from our email list at the bottom of each email update, on our site at the 'email update' section, or by emailing webmaster@mercycorps.org with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

**Online Donations**

Our goal is to forge a long-term partnership with you. Your donations make the Mercy Corps mission possible. We value and appreciate the trust that accompanies your online donation. The information you provide (your name, address, email, etc.) is stored in a secure location and protected by security procedures. It will never be sold or rented to a third party. To serve you better, we may contact you in the future to inform you about Mercy Corps' response to the needs of the world's suffering people. We will offer various mailing options, so you can choose how often you hear from us. Mercy Corps will remove your name from our mailing list, email list or telephone solicitation list at any time, at your request. We also publish a summary of our financial statements each year in our Annual Report, and our complete financial statement will be available upon request at any time. Mercy Corps uses the services of outside vendors to complete the online donation process. These vendors adhere to Mercy Corps' commitment to privacy and security. However, if you should have a concern please contact us directly, and we will do our utmost to correct the problem.

Thank you for your interest in Mercy Corps and our privacy policy. If you would like more information about the options discussed herein or simply have questions, please feel free to contact us via email at info@mercycorps.org, or speak to a Donor Services Representative at 800.292.3355 x 250. 

Printer-friendly Version: Privacy Policy

* * *

Mercy Corps exists to alleviate suffering, poverty and oppression by helping people build secure, productive and just communities. Since 1979, Mercy Corps has provided more than $640 million in aid to 74 nations. The agency currently reaches more than 5 million people in over 30 countries. More than 91 percent of the Mercy Corps' resources are allocated to programs that help those in need.
Privacy Policy

Our goal at Mercy Corps is to extend trust and respect to you on the web. We are committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our website. The following information details Mercy Corps' collection, protection, and use of the data we receive from visitors to this website. 

**Email Updates**

Emergency program updates provide a worldwide perspective on the Mercy Corps mission to alleviate suffering, poverty, and oppression around the globe. In order to receive these updates you must provide Mercy Corps with your email address. Rest assured, your email will be used for emergency and program purposes only, and we will NOT sell, rent or trade this information to a third party. Certain email update promotional activities may require your name for database recognition purposes. This information will be held in complete confidence, and it will NOT be sold, rented or traded. In addition, you will be given the option to remove your name from our email list at the bottom of each email update, on our site at the 'email update' section, or by emailing webmaster@mercycorps.org with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Online Donations**

Our goal is to forge a long-term partnership with you. Your donations make the Mercy Corps mission possible. We value and appreciate the trust that accompanies your online donation. The information you provide (your name, address, email, etc.) is stored in a secure location and protected by security procedures. It will never be sold or rented to a third party. To serve you better, we may contact you in the future to inform you about Mercy Corps' response to the needs of the world's suffering people. We will offer various mailing options, so you can choose how often you hear from us. Mercy Corps will remove your name from our mailing list, email list or telephone solicitation list at any time, at your request. We also publish a summary of our financial statements each year in our Annual Report, and our complete financial statement will be available upon request at any time. Mercy Corps uses the services of outside vendors to complete the online donation process. These vendors adhere to Mercy Corps' commitment to privacy and security. However, if you should have a concern please contact us directly, and we will do our utmost to correct the problem. 

Thank you for your interest in Mercy Corps and our privacy policy. If you would like more information about the options discussed herein or simply have questions, please feel free to contact us via email at info@mercycorps.org, or speak to a Donor Services Representative at 800.292.3355 x 250.

|
